I
Feel my way through the darkness
Got it by beating hard I
Ain't tell where the journey will end
But I know where to start
They tell me I'm too young to understand
It's them caught up in a dream
Well, I will pass me by if I don't open up my eyes
So that's fine by me
So wake me up when it's all over
When I'm wise I ran out of water
All this time I was finding myself
Didn't know I was long
So wake me up when it's all over
When I'm wise I ran out of water
All this time I was finding myself
And I didn't know I was long
They don't like us
Yeah, I know
Why?
Yeah
I try to carry in the weight of the world
But I only have two hands
On my get the chance to travel the world
I don't have any plans
Wish that I could stay forever this young
Not afraid to close my eyes
Life's a game made for everyone
And love is a prize
So wake me up when it's all over
When I'm wise I ran out of water
All this time I was finding myself
And I didn't know I was long
So wake me up when it's all over
When I'm wise I ran out of water
All this time I was finding myself
And I didn't know I was long
I didn't know I was long
Get up, I killed things
Where are we going?
Somewhere with the lawn
So I ran out of water
All this time I was finding myself
And I didn't know I was long
I didn't know I was long
But I only have two hands
So I ran out of water